{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Fill in the missing animals in these movie titles. ",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Apes",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "Planet of the ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Snakes",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "______ on a Plane"
  }, {
    "answer": "Dalmatians",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "101 __________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Chipmunks",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "Alvin and the _________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lambs",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "The Silence of the _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Panther",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "The Pink _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Crocodile",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "_________ Dundee"
  }, {
    "answer": "Horse",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "The _____ Whisperer"
  }, {
    "answer": "Dogs",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "All ____ Go to Heaven"
  }, {
    "answer": "Wolves",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "Dances with ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Cuckoo",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "One Flew Over the ______'s Nest"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bull",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "Raging ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Fish",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "A ____ Called Wanda"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bird",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "____ on a Wire"
  }, {
    "answer": "Penguins",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "March of the ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Butterfly",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "The _________ Effect"
  }, {
    "answer": "Mouse",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "The Great _____ Detective"
  }, {
    "answer": "Ducks",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "The Mighty _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bears",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "The Bad News _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Cobra",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "G.I. Joe: The Rise of _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Pelican",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "The _______ Brief"
  }, {
    "answer": "Eagles",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "Where ______ Dare"
  }, {
    "answer": "Rabbit",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "______-Proof Fence"
  }, {
    "answer": "Hawk",
    "category": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
    "question": "Hudson ____"
  }],
  "quizLength": 24,
  "title": "Movies with Animals in the Title",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/movies-with-animals-quiz.php"
}